Postcards
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Postcards, 2.1.7
  - United States of America (Pennsylvania), undated; 3 (Box 1602)
    - Verso: Independence Hall, on Chestnut & Fifth streets, erected in 1729, contains the National Museum and Liberty Bell. Here was debated and signed the Declaration of Independence on July 4th, 1776., 1-verso
  - United States of America (South Carolina), undated; 4 (Box 1602)
    - Courtyard view, St. John Hotel, Charleston, S.C., 1
    - Verso: South Courtyard View of St. John Hotel, Charleston, S.C., 115 Meeting Street at Queen. Phone 7741., 1-verso
    - Courtyard view, St. John Hotel, Charleston, S.C., 2
    - Verso [South Courtyard View of St. John Hotel Charleston, S.C., 115 Meeting Street at Queen. Phone 7741.], 2-verso
  - United States of America (South Dakota), undated; 5 (Box 1602)
    - The Evans Hotel-Hot Springs, South Dakota, 1
    - Verso: The Evans Hotel. Ward E. Parsons, Mgr. [Manager]. Hot Spring, South Dekota, The City of Healing Water. Southern gateway to the Black Hills. 148 Rooms. Rates from $1.50 Rooms without bath. from $2.00 Rooms with bath. South Dakota's only hotel with pure mineral spring water in every room.], 1-verso
    - Mt. [Mount] Rushmore National Memorial, Black Hills, So. [South] Dak. [Dakota], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
  - United States of America (Alta, Utah), undated; 6 (Box 1602)
    - [Alta, Utah. High Rustler, Wildcat and Collins Chairlifts], 1
    - Verso: Alta, Utah. High Rustler, Wildcat and Collins Chairlifts.], 1-verso
    - [Alta, Utah. Wildcat Lift from the top of Sunspot], 2
    - Verso: Alta, Utah. Wildcat Lift from the top of Sunspot.], 2-verso
  - United States of America (Stowe, Vermont) [Lowell Thomas broadcasting winter sports], circa 1960s; 7 (Box 1602)
    - Lowell Thomas broadcasting winter sports, Stowe, V.T., 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Lowell Thomas broadcasting winter sports, Stowe, V.T., 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - Lowell Thomas broadcasting winter sports, Stowe, V.T., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
  - United States of America (Virginia), undated; 8 (Box 1602)
    - Williamsburg Lodge, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1
    - Verso: Williamsburg Lodge, Williamsburg, Virginia. This attractive modern hotel, owned and operated by Williamsburg Restoration, Inc., features rooms and meals at moderate prices, Coffee Shop and special facilities for tour parties.], 1-verso
    - Home of Washington. Mt. Vernon V.A., 2
    - Verso: MOUNT VERNON, the Home of Washington is on the Virginia shore of the Potomac, 16 miles south of the Capitol. The second story end window is of the room in which Washington died. The window above is of attic room occupied by Mrs. Washington after her husband's death and chosen because the window overlooked his tomb.], 2-verso
  - United States of America (Washington), undated; 9 (Box 1602)
    - Lake Sutterlano, Washington, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Falling a spruce in Clallam Co. [Country] Wash. [Washington], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - Wha lLath-[Indian in headdress], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - Cedar stump on the Elwah River used by pioneers as a post office, 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - Two patriots of Clallam Co. [Country] Wash. [Washington], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - Arch at Cape Elizabeth, north from Moclips, Wash. [Washington], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - Mill. Port Angeles], 7
    - Verso [Blank back of postcard], 7-verso
  - United States of America (Washington, D.C.), undated; 10 (Box 1602)
    - Lincoln Memorial and Mirror Pool, Washington D.C., 1
    - Verso: Lincoln Memorial is located on the axis of the Capitol and the Monument. The union of the U.S. is expressed in the colonnade surrounding the hall. There are 36 columns, one for each State in the existance at the time of Lincoln's death. The statue of Lincoln is in the center of the Memorial, while smaller halls at each sideof the central hall contain second Inaugural and Gettysburg Address., 1-verso
    - United States Capitol, Washington D.C., 2
    - Verso: The U.S. Capitol at Washington, D.C., was begin in 1793, the cornerstone of which was laid by Geroge Washington. The central building was finished in 1800, one wing in 1811, and was burned by the British in 1814. It ranks today among the noblest architectural objects in the world, its crowning glory being the Statue of Freedom which surmounts its dome 307 feet above the esplanade. At one end of the U.S. Senate, at the other the U.S. House of Representatives, the combined duties of whose members represent the greatest governmental undertaking in the world. It is 751 feet in length and 350 feet in width and covers an area of three and one-half acres. On its east central portico the oath of office is administered to each succeeding President by the Chief Justice of the U.S. Supreme Court before a multitude of spectators., 2-verso
  - United States of America (Wyoming), undated; 11 (Box 1602)
    - A "dude" ranch in the Big Horn Mountains of Wyoming--Where eastern city men live at the homes of ranchers, become cow-boys on their vacations and enjoy outdoor life par excellence, on horseback, while improving physically. Burlington Route-Direct to the Big Horns, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - A "dude" ranch in the Big Horn Mountains of Wyoming-where eastern city men live at the homes of ranchers, become cow-boys on their vacations and enjoy outdoor life par excellence, on horseback, while improving physically. Burlington Route-Direct to the Big Horns, 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
  - Advertisements for "With Allenby in Palestine", circa 1919; 12 (Box 1602)
    - Colonel Lawrence and Lowell Thomas in Arabia., 1
    - Verso: Percy Burton presents Lowell Thomas in his wonderful illustrated travelogue of the British campaign with Allenby in Palestine & Arabia. Most wonderful of human stories. Marvellous moving pictures. Covent Gardent Royal Opera House. Nightly 8:30 sharp. Matinees Tues., Wed., Thurs. and Sat. at 2:30 sharp., 1-verso
    - F.M. Sir Edmund Allenby and Mr. Lowell Thomas, 2
    - Verso [Percy Burton presents Lowell Thomas in his wonderful illustrated travelogue of the British campaign with Allenby in Palestine & Arabia. Most wonderful of human stories. Marvellous moving pictures. Covent Gardent Royal Opera House. Nightly 8:30 sharp. Matinees Tues., Wed., Thurs. and Sat. at 2:30 sharp.], 2-verso
  - The Bohemian Club, undated; 13 (Box 1602)
    - [Members of the Bohemian Club], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Three members of the Bohemian Club standing under a large tree.], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Pond at the Bohemian Club], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [Three members of the Bohemian Club], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Members of the Bohemian Club; Aviary], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
  - Coronation King George, 1937 May 12; 14 (Box 1602)
    - Their Majesties the King and Queen with the Princesses in coronation robes, 1
    - Verso: Prints flown to Dundee by aeroplane on Coronation Day, May 12th, 1937. Post cards on sale in London by 11 o' clock on 13th May. With all the old-time historic pomp and pageantry and amid the plaudits of their loyal peoples, Their Gracious Majesties King George VI. and Queen Elizabeth were crowned within the Abbey of Westminster this 12th day of May 1937, whereof this is a memento., 1-verso
  - Cunard R.M.S. Lancastria, circa 1926; 15 (Box 1602)
    - Cunard R.M.S. Lancastria. Tonnage 16,500, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Note [Letter from Frances Ryan Thomas to her parents, June 1926. See Frances Ryan Thomas's correspondence to parents-June 1926-for original], 2
    - Note [Letter from Frances Ryan Thomas to her parents, June 1926. See Frances Ryan Thomas's correspondence to parents-June 1926-for original], 3
    - Note [Letter from Frances Ryan Thomas to her parents, June 1926. See Frances Ryan Thomas's correspondence to parents-June 1926-for original], 4
    - Note [Letter from Frances Ryan Thomas to her parents, June 1926. See Frances Ryan Thomas's correspondence to parents-June 1926-for original], 5
  - Early friends, undated; 16 (Box 1602)
    - Mort. Roberts, Tahis Car, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
  - European Skyways, 1926; 17 (Box 1602)
    - Alan J. Cobam, 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Alan J. Cobham, 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - Verkeersvliegtuig [scouting airplane] der K.L.M. type Fokker F-111, 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [Fokker airplane before landing at Innsbruck, Germany], 4
    - Verso [Fokker before landing at Innsbruck], 4-verso
    - [Aerial photo of Achensee, Lake Achen, Austria], 5
    - Verso: Achcnsee, 5-verso
    - [Innsbruck Aerodrome], 6
    - Verso: Innsbruck Aerodrome, 6-verso
  - Albert Gallatin, undated; 18 (Box 1602)
    - Albert Gallatin, 1
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built in 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania.], 1-verso
    - Albert Gallatin, 2
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built in 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania.], 2-verso
    - Old Side Board; State Dining Room, 3
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 3-verso
    - Lafayette Room, 4
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 4-verso
    - State Dining Room, 5
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 5-verso
    - Original Dining Room 1789, 6
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 6-verso
    - Old Side Board; State Dining Room, 7
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 7-verso
    - Original Dinging Room 1789, 8
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 8-verso
    - State Dining Room, 9
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 9-verso
    - Drawing Room, 10
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 10-verso
    - Bedroom, 11
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 11-verso
    - Lafayette Room, 12
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 12-verso
    - Bedroom, 13
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 13-verso
    - Bedroom, 14
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 14-verso
    - Rear View of Mansion, 15
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 15-verso
    - Entrance Drive, Winter Scene, 16
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 16-verso
    - The Lookout overlooking Mononghela River, 17
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 17-verso
    - Grave of Sophia Allegre, First Wife of Albert Gallatin, 18
    - Verso: "Friendship Hill" Home of Albert Gallatin, Secretary of the U.S. Treasury under Thomas Jefferson and James Madison, Minister to France, Minister to England and the controlling person in negotiating and concluding the Treaty of Ghent which closed the War of 1812. Built 1789, near New Geneva, Pennsylvania., 18-verso
  - The Jackson family, undated; 19 (Box 1602)
    - [Rollo, Effie, Una, Lulu, Debra, Earl, Edith Oran [?]; Rollo & Jackson children], 1
    - Verso: Rollo, Effie, Una, Lulu, Debra, Earl, Edith Oran [?]; Rollo & Jackson children, 1-verso
    - [Laurd Edith Earl (the twins) Dad Jackson], 2
    - Verso: Laura, Edith, Earl (the twins), Dad, Jackson, 2-verso
  - T. E. Lawrence (tomb), undated; 20 (Box 1602)
    - [T.E. Lawrence's tomb. St. Martin's, Wareham, Dorset], 1
    - Verso: T.E. Lawrence. St. Martin's, Wareham, Dorset, by Erik Kennington, 1-verso
    - [T.E. Lawrence's tomb. St. Martin's, Wareham, Dorset], 2
    - Verso: T.E. Lawrence. St. Martin's, Wareham, Dorset, by Erik Kennington, 2-verso
    - [T.E. Lawrence's tomb. St. Martin's, Wareham, Dorset], 3
    - Verso [T.E. Lawrence. St. Martin's, Wareham, Dorset, by Erik Kennington], 3-verso
  - James E. Oliver [photographer], undated; 21 (Box 1602)
    - [Signing of the Treaty of Greenville August 3, 1795], 1
    - Verso: Signing of the treaty of Greene Ville, August 3, 1795. Taken from an original painting by Howard Chandler Christy that is now on display at Garst Museum in Greenville, Ohio., 1-verso
    - [Little Turtle-Michikiniqua], 2
    - Verso: Little Turtle-Michikiniqua. A Chief of the Miami Inidan trive, who signed the Treat of Greene Ville on August 3, 1795. Taken from a painting at Garst Museum in Greenville, Ohio., 2-verso
    - [Major General Anthony Wayne], 3
    - Verso: Major General Anthony Wayne; Commander-in-chief of the American army that defeated the confederated Indian tribes at Fallen Timbers in 1794. He negotiated for and concluded the signing of the peace Treaty of Greene Ville on August 3, 1795, 3-verso
  - Norman Ryan, circa 1917; 22 (Box 1602)
    - [Norman Ryan], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Norman Ryan], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Norman Ryan and a dog], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [Norman Ryan and a dog], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Norman Ryan and a dog], [20 additional copies], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
  - Lowell Thomas [portrait painting], undated; 23 (Box 1602)
    - [Portrait of Lowell Thomas], 1
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas born April 6, 1892 in Woodington, Ohio 5 miles northwest of Greenville. Famous news commentator, world traveler and author. Painting on display at Garst Museum, Greenville, Ohio.], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas], 2
    - Verso: Lowell Thomas born April 6, 1892 in Woodington, Ohio 5 miles northwest of Greenville. Famous news commentator, world traveler and author. Painting on display at Garst Museum, Greenville, Ohio.], 2-verso
  - Lowell Thomas publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover], 1931 September 19; 24 (Box 1602)
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], [72 additional copies], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
  - Lowell Thomas publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover], 1931 September 19; 25 (Box 1602)
    - [Lowell Thomas publicity photograph], [70 additional copies], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
  Box 1603
- Postcards, 2.1.7
  - Lowell Thomas publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover], 1931 September 19; 1 (Box 1603)
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], [many additional copies], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
  - Lowell Thomas publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover], 1931 September 19; 2 (Box 1603)
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], [many additional copies], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
  - Lowell Thomas publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover], 1931 September 19; 3 (Box 1603)
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], [many additional copies], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
  - Lowell Thomas publicity photographs [Literary Digest cover], 1931 September 19; 4 (Box 1603)
    - [Lowell Thomas posing with safari hat], [many additional copies], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
  - The Thomas family, circa 1910s - 1930s; 5 (Box 1603)
    - [Young Lowell Thomas and friends at the beach], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - [Group of Military nen], 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - [Young girl with a dog], 3
    - Verso: Bobbie and I are coming to meet you brother dear., 3-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, young Lowell Thomas, Jr. and two men on a sled], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - [Lowell Thomas, young Lowell Thomas, Jr. and Frances Ryan Thomas on horses], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
  - Miscellaneous postcards, undated; 6 (Box 1603)
    - [Group of 17 skulls], 1
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 1-verso
    - Harpooned Sperm [Whale] P.B.B., 2
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 2-verso
    - Harpooned Sperm [Whale] P.B.B., 3
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 3-verso
    - Now what's that? [Man holding a bowl up to a bear cub on a pole], 4
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 4-verso
    - "My turn next." [Man giving a bottle to a bear cub], 5
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 5-verso
    - "Please take off the chain." [Bear cub holding on to a man's arm], 6
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 6-verso
    - [Two boys and an Alaskan sled with 9 dogs], 7
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 7-verso
    - [Docked sailboat], 8
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 8-verso
    - [Buildings on a hillside with many smokestacks], 9
    - Verso: [back of postcard], 9-verso
    - Our Christian Era. This Painting by F. Luis Mora, on display at the DUN & BRADSTREET, INC. exhibit at the New York World's Fair, is eight feet in height by six feet in breadth. F. Luis Mora, N.A., was born in south America, the son of Domingo Mora, a distinguished Spanish sculptor. The murals, portraits, and water colors of F. Luis Mora appear in many public buildings, museums, and art galleries throughout the United States., 10
    - Verso: Our Christian Era. Christianity is the invinceable bulwark against fear, hatred, avarice, politics, purpose, cruelty in peace, selfishness, misunderstanding. Line after line of marchers, down, down, our Christian calendar; panoplied youth in armor, here and there a sword hilt graved by a heart that loved beauty, beauty used for the kill, chasulbles of broidered gold with jewels, candelabra of gold, candles for prayers and everywhere the symbol of the Cross. Armies of thousands upon thousands, marching, marching, marching. Drums, bugles and more drums. Yes! And flags, flags everywhere. Shining bayonets guilded by the sunset. Prayers for victory in the murderous battlefield and bombing the houses of God. Bodies frozen in moats of the dark ages and in the shell holes of today. On the mount sits that tired, saddened, lonely figure, still compassionate, stil asking, "Forgive them for they know not what they do." (The above wording appears in the panel of the painting), 10-verso
    - Our Christian Era. This Painting by F. Luis Mora, on display at the DUN & BRADSTREET, INC. exhibit at the New York World's Fair, is eight feet in height by six feet in breadth. F. Luis Mora, N.A., was born in south America, the son of Domingo Mora, a distinguished Spanish sculptor. The murals, portraits, and water colors of F. Luis Mora appear in many public buildings, museums, and art galleries throughout the United States., 11